export default {
    
        "all_questions": [
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": ["Central Processing Unit",false],
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": "181913649",
                "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
                "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit",
                "incorrect_answers":[
                    "Central Process Unit",
                    "Computer Personal Unit",
                    "Central Processor Unit"
                ]
            },
        ]
    }
